yeah it's gonna be a really short
periscope cuz it's not quite ready yet
but guys I just got my Aeon in the mail
this thing is awesome like this thing is
super nice I think you're gonna be happy
with it you know I got I got Spotify
here I got ways over here just give a
second to load here I drove home with
one of these on Schaffer plus shipper
plus is nice it's pretty nice yes press
combo you go home your settings menu so
yeah you'll be able to do things like
naval phone collision warning honeywell
ssh so you can turn ssh on the off Wi-Fi
notice the Bluetooth settings your eon
is going to support bluetooth connecting
it to your car this one does have a Sun
coordinate it will also work without a
SIM card and Neos I know need SIM cards
at least like boot logged out I can
reset my calibration there's my dongle
ID yeah but it's not quite finished yet
but we're getting close like check out
the new sidebar doesn't that look nice
to be able to just press new destination
it will take you right here two ways it
shows your current destination on this
screen like the weather right here it
knows where you are yeah yeah it's based
off it's based off of one Plus Android
device of course it's just logging here
I like to Spotify a throwaway for
Spotify you know I'm not gonna shake as
my secret Spotify login you
what's up
so you just log in same way I'd log into
anything else in my Spotify
check it out bros of course you probably
want to do this over over bluetooth the
unity on sound system exists it's good
enough for ways and be probable turns
into a console system we also support
the old school that's a headphone jack
so you can plug that right into your car
or your radio thing losing like pop
songs but quick periscope just want to
tell you guys how excited I am that I
got my tea on in the mail today and it's
pretty cool that's that thanks for
watching